acc.com 2002-06-03

# Privacy

|   |    
---|---  
**Jump to**  
|  Information collection and use   
|  Browsing   
|  Subscriptions   
|  Order, surveys and contests   
|  Individuals' use of extranet   
|  External links   
|  Changes to Ericsson's internet privacy policy   
|  How to contact Ericsson about this privacy policy   
|  |  | At Ericsson, we understand that privacy is an important issue for visitors to the Ericsson Web site [www.ericsson.com](http://www.ericsson.com/). The following information is designed to help visitors understand what information we gather from our site, and how we handle the information once we gather it. |   
---|---|---  
|  Information collection and use  |   
|  |   
|    
Ericsson is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ericsson may collect information from our users at several different points on our website.   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Browsing  |   
|  |   
|    
Cookies are small text files that a Web site transfers to a site visitor's hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking Web site usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person's name or e-mail address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, Ericsson may use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our Web site, and to determine the path visitors take on our site. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis. Examples include:   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Subscriptions  |   
|  |   
|    
If a user wishes to subscribe to Ericsson information such as press releases or financial reports, we ask for an email address. Ericsson will use this e-mail address only to send the requested information; we will not send other unsolicited information.   
  
How to cancel your subscription - users who no longer wish to receive our information may cancel their subscription(s) at any time. You can unsubscribe by replying with 'unsubscribe' in the subject line in the email, or by sending an email to us at majordomo@www.ericsson.se   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Order, surveys and contests  |   
|  |   
|    
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.   
  
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. **These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.**   
  
From time to time our site may request information from users via contests or surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as gender, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers.   
  
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Individuals' use of extranet  |   
|  |   
|    
Extranets provide customer specific content and functions. In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our major customers, we must mutually agree on which of their personnel may use specific Extranet functions. Ericsson uses cookies, together with additional security mechanisms, to identify and track the registered users who enter Extranet portions of www.ericsson.com.   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  External links  |   
|  |   
|    
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Ericsson is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Changes to Ericsson's internet privacy policy  |   
|  |   
|    
Ericsson may, from time to time, make changes to this policy. We recommend that visitors to this site re-visit this privacy policy on occasion to learn of new privacy practices or changes to our policy.   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  How to contact Ericsson about this privacy policy  |   
|  |   
|    
It's important to us at Ericsson to hear what visitors have to say about our services, and our policies. If site visitors have any questions, concerns, or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or want to let us know what they think about any of our off-line and on-line products and services, they can use our "Questions and Comments" form accessible from almost every page on this site..   
  
|   
|   Top |   
|  |   
|  Last published March 01, 2002  |   
|
